# DEVYN HANNA, B.E.S., MS. C.

devynhanna@gmail.com • devynhanna.com • 647-920-3664 • Brampton, Ontario

# PROFILE SUMMARY

A highly resourceful and ambitious planning graduate with over 10 years of customer service experience and 4 years of management and training experience. Possesses expertise in the field of urban and regional environments in both the United Kingdom and Canadian planning systems. Excellent at collecting, analysing, interpreting, and presenting city planning data and information. Proficient knowledge of Geographical Information systems and sufficient knowledge of Adobe Photoshop. In possession of strong interpersonal skills which is an asset for both public consultations and working with members of a team.

## **EDUCATION**

Master of Science December 2018

Planning and Regeneration with Distinction

Queens University Belfast, Belfast, Northern Ireland

#### **Honours Bachelor of Environmental Studies**

June 2015

Specification in Urban and Regional Environments

York University, Toronto, ON

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### **Remote Support Representative**

August 2018 – Present

Disney Consumer Product & Interactive Media, Kelowna, BC

- Works alongside a team of support representatives for Disney based programs such as Movies Anywhere and ESPN+
- Responsible for providing exceptional Disney experiences by being the main point of contact to users; turning each interaction over phone, email or live chat into a meaningful connection with guests.
- Ranked among the top communication respondents of the support team.
- Responsible for day-to-day communications over Slack, Salesforce, Zendesk and Outlook.
  The role also includes extensive use of the Microsoft Office Suite.

### Le Cellier Signature Dining Server

**March 2016 – April 2017** 

Walt Disney World Resort, Florida, USA

- Participant in the Cultural Representative Program; a one-year contract to work in Epcot in the Canada Pavilion sharing Canadian culture.
- Trained in the Disney Signature Dining Standards which aided in extensive food and wine knowledge.
- Responsible for training new cast members in dining standards.

## **Assistant Manager**

March 2010 - March 2016

Cineplex Entertainment, Brampton, ON

- Part of the management team for both Guest Service and Food Services at the cinema.
- Largely responsible for guest satisfaction and recovery.
- Responsible for the distribution of daily cast member duties, cinema stock ordering, and daily cash flow via Cash Desk.
- Role included extensive use of Microsoft Office Suite, Infor and ADP for maintaining administrative duties, such as scheduling, payroll, and accounts payable.

#### **Merchandise Hostess**

May 2014 – August 2014

Walt Disney World Resort, Florida, USA

- Participant in the International College Summer Work Experience Program.
- Extensive interpersonal experience gained from guest interactions as a part of front of house responsibilities.
- This work also included extensive cash handling, and guest services.
- Additionally, as a member of the back of house operations, this role included stocking stores regularly throughout the day and unpacking daily shipments.

#### **Attractions Hostess**

May 2012 – August 2012

Walt Disney World Resort, Florida, USA

- Participant in the International College Summer Work Experience Program.
- Responsible for the safe operation of the Magic Carpets of Aladdin, Walt Disney's Enchanted Tiki Room, and The Swiss Robinson Family Tree House attractions.
- Upheld the standards of the Walt Disney Company including but not limited to the 4 Keys: Safety, Efficiency, Show, and Courtesy.
- Included extensive interactions with guests and their families in order to create magical moments while on vacation while also meeting all their needs.